Hi there. I'm Anthony, and I'm the product lead for
大家好 我叫 Anthony 是优达学城
intro to self-driving cars here at Udacity.
无人驾驶车入门课程的产品主管
I'm excited to help start your journey towards becoming a self-driving car engineer.
我很高兴能够和你一起 开启无人驾驶工程师之旅
There's a lot of work that goes into making this great Nanodegree program.
这个纳米学位项目非常棒 我们为此做了很多工作
And we want to take a few moments to introduce
现在 我希望花一点时间来向你介绍一下
you to the team who helped make this possible.
项目背后的团队
Hi, I'm Andy. I'm the curriculum lead for this project.
大家好 我叫 Andy 是这个项目的课程主管
I've been teaching and learning at Udacity for five years.
我在优达学城已经教学了 5 年
And self-driving cars are a world changing technology.
无人驾驶汽车是一项改变世界的技术
And the mathematics and computer science principles that underlie them are fascinating.
其中蕴含着十分吸引人的数学和计算机科学原理
I really can't wait to introduce you to this incredible world.
我已经迫不及待要向你介绍这个神奇的世界
Hi, I'm Cezanne Camacho.
大家好 我叫 Cezanne Camacho
And I'm a content developer at Udacity.
我是优达学城的一名课程内容设计师
I'm an expert in computer vision which is how machines,
也是一名计算机视觉专家 主要研究
like self-driving cars, visually perceive and respond to the world.
无人驾驶汽车这类的机器如何从视觉上感知这个世界并做出相应的回应
And I'm excited to teach you about vision and other foundational programming,
我很高兴教授你计算机视觉和其有关的基础编程知识
and math concepts that
以及一些相关的数学概念
all self-driving cars rely on when they make decisions on the road.
这些数学概念是所有无人驾驶汽车在行驶中进行决策时所必需的
Hi, I'm Elecia White.
大家好 我叫 Elecia White
I'm an embedded systems engineer with
我是一名工作 20 多年的嵌入式系统工程师
over 20 years of experience in all sorts of industries.
我在各类工业领域中都有过嵌入式系统开发的相关经验
I wrote "Making Embedded Systems" for O'Reilly.
我曾经为 O'Reilly 公司撰写《Making Embedded Systems》一书
And I host embedded.fm - a podcast about the many aspects of the engineering.
另外我还经营着 embeded.fm 这个在线播客 包含了涉及工程的方方面面
I'm here to help you understand why
在这里 我将帮助你理解为什么
C++ is so important in the development of self-driving cars.
C++ 语言在无人驾驶车的开发中如此重要
Hi, I'm Tarin. I'm a director of AI here at Voyage.
大家好 我叫 Tarin 是 Voyage 的人工智能总监
And I'm super excited to joining a classroom and
我十分荣幸能够参与到这样一个课程中来
teach about machine learning and computer vision.
来讲授机器学习和计算机视觉的相关知识
Hi, I'm Jessica. I'm the program manager for
大家好 我叫 Jessica 是无人驾驶入门基石纳米学位
your Nanodegree program as well as for the self-driving car engineer Nanodegree program.
和无人驾驶工程师纳米学位的项目负责人
I'm really looking forward to having you in the program,
非常欢迎你加入这个纳米学位
and really excited for you as you start this journey.
我十分高兴能和你一起开始这场学习之旅
If you ever need anything from me,
如果你需要了解任何事情
you can come find me in Slack community.
可以在 Slack 社区找到我
Hi, I'm Erika.
大家好 我是 Erika 00:01:43,740 --&gt; 00:01:45,450. 我是一名学生服务助理
Feel free to ping me on Slack,
你可以在 Slack 上联系我
or email at support@udacity.com
或者发送电子邮件至 support@udacity.com
There are even more people behind
我们在幕后有更多的员工
the scenes that are doing everything they can to make
正在竭尽全力 完善这个学位项目
this program great. Now, what do you say we get started?
现在 我们开始学习吧